http://www.orangecu.com.au/privacy

Electronic Banking
Access via Internet Banking, Phone Banking, SMS Alerts, or our Mobile App
Access cards
Access your funds with a Orange Debit Card, or add extra funds through a Credit Card
Deposits & Withdrawals
Orange Credit Union provides a range of options to send and receive money
Payments
BPAY, Cheque, Direct Debit, EFTPOS, Periodical Payments, External Transfers
Transaction Accounts
Access your money, your way with our Everyday Bank Account range
Rates and Fees
Compare rates and fees across our range of accounts, loans, and more
Bank with us
We can help you create or switch your bank account to Orange Credit Union
Transaction Accounts
Access your money, your way with our Everyday Bank Account range
Savings Accounts
Maximise your monthly earnings by earning interest with a Savings Account
Investment Accounts
Get guaranteed interest for a specified period of time with a Term Deposit
Government Guarantee
Orange meets the same standards as all Australian banks and credit unions
Financial Planning
Meet with a financial planner, create goals, and make them a reality
Home Loans
Apply for a Fixed or Variable Rate Home Loan, or select a Home Loan Option
Car Loans
New and Used Car Loans for your dream car, caravan, boat or motorcycle
Personal Loans
Select a Secured, Part-Secured or Unsecured Personal Loan based your needs
Overdraft Facilities
Get access to additional funds, up to an approved limit, with an Overdraft
Insurance
We are partnered with QBE and Zurich to bring members flexible coverage
Financial Planning
Meet with a financial planner, create goals, and make them a reality
International Services
Travelling overseas? Everything you need before you leave the country
Apply Now
Register to become a member, open an account, or apply for a loan online
Forms
All online and PDF application forms, as well important documents
Calculators
Calculators, planners and tools to help you better manage your money
Banking Guides
Help guides for Internet Banking, Mobile Banking, Online Security, and more
Product FAQs
Find answers to common member questions, or submit a question of your own
Resolving problems
Reach out to us if something is troubling you about our relationship with you
Resolving problems
Reach out to us if something is troubling you about our relationship with you
BSB 802 129
Home
/ Privacy
Privacy
In handling your personal information, Orange Credit Union is committed to complying with the Privacy Act 1988, the Australian Privacy Principles and the Customer Owned Banking Code of Practice.
View our Privacy Policy and Privacy Notification for more information.
Request a Call Contact us
Collection and use of personal information
We collect and hold personal information about you to:
provide you with membership benefits, financial services and products or information about those benefits, services and products
provide you with information about financial services and products from 3rd parties we have arrangements with
conduct market or customer satisfaction research.
The law also requires us to collect and hold personal information about you:
for our register of members
to verify your identity
to assess your capacity to pay a loan you have applied for and is guaranteed
Collection and Use of loan repayment history
We will also collect information about your repayment history when you have a loan with us – whether you have paid on time, when payments are due and when you have paid. We may disclose this information to credit reporting agencies from March 2014.
Providing your personal information to other organisations
In providing our financial services and products to you, it may be necessary for us to disclose your personal information to other organisations. We only disclose your personal information to the extent necessary and to the extent required by law. The types of organisations that we can disclose your personal information to are:
organisations that provide information to verify your identity
credit reporting agencies and other financial institutions that have previously lent you
brokers and agents who have referred your business to us
persons you name as referees, or your employer, in loan applications
property valuers and insurers for property loans
lenders mortgage insurers
mortgage documentation service
trustee and manager of securitised loan programs
your guarantor
debt collection agencies, lawyers, process servers
contractors for statement printing and mail out, card and cheque production, market research or direct marketing
3rd party product suppliers to provide information to you about their services and products
Credit reporting agencies
The credit reporting agency we provide information to is Equifax.
Your rights
You may access your personal information at any time by asking us. We may charge you a fee for this. If you ask us to correct any personal information we hold, we will do so, and without cost to you.
What if you do not wish to provide us with information?
If you do not give us the personal information we require, we may not be able to admit you to membership or provide you with the financial service or product you have applied for.
Quick links
Apply Online
Products
Calculators
Rates & Fees
Special Offers
Apply Now
Membership
Earn competitive interest rates.
Enter a loan amount, interest rate and repayment frequency to calculate a repayment estimate
Car Loan
Get an idea of how much you can borrow and your repayments
Personal Loan
Calculate how much you might be able to borrow for personal use
I love that it is local and looks after local people and even though I have moved I do not want to let go of OCU as I feel it is a part of read more
All the staff are friendly and will always help you
It is situated locally; all the staff are friendly and will always help you. Your money stays in town and is used to help someone who is a read more
For the last 40 + years
For the last 40 + years I have banked with the credit union and the big majority of all money loans that I have had, have been through the read more
